<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>In the heart of Europe runs the purest stream of human love, of justice, of spirit of self-sacrifice for higher ideals. In Europe we have seen noble minds who have ever stood up for the rights of man irrespective of colour and creed. (Rabindranath Tagore) on Europe 27</title>
    <link>https://evropa27.org/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in In the heart of Europe runs the purest stream of human love, of justice, of spirit of self-sacrifice for higher ideals. In Europe we have seen noble minds who have ever stood up for the rights of man irrespective of colour and creed. (Rabindranath Tagore) on Europe 27</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://evropa27.org/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://evropa27.org/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://evropa27.org/en/about/</guid>
      <description>The Lodge Europe is a Freemasonic Lodge established in the Orient of Belgrade with the number 27, under the auspices of the Regular Grand Lodge of Serbia, on October 3, 2009. The founding idea was to create a Lodge of young people who would embody the progressive values of Europe, aiming to bring Free Masons and citizens of Serbia closer, at a right angle, to a better future in a united Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About ISEL</title>
      <link>https://evropa27.org/en/post/about_isel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://evropa27.org/en/post/about_isel/</guid>
      <description>The International Symposium of European Lodges (ISEL) is an international organization that brings together Lodges bearing the name &amp;ldquo;Europe&amp;rdquo; and operating under the auspices of Regular Grand Lodges. The first symposium, where ISEL was founded, was held in Riccione from May 9 to 11, 2008. Six Lodges from Italy, Austria, France, and Romania gathered on the initiative of the Brethren from Lodge Europe No. 765 in the Orient of Riccione. In the following years, new Lodges from other European countries joined, so today ISEL comprises over 20 Lodges from Italy, Austria, France, Romania, Serbia, Hungary, Bosnia and Herzegovina, Greece, Spain, Belgium, Slovenia, and Montenegro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activites</title>
      <link>https://evropa27.org/en/post/activities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://evropa27.org/en/post/activities/</guid>
      <description>Lodge Europe No. 27 in the Orient of Belgrade operates under the auspices of the Regular Grand Lodge of Serbia and participates in many humanitarian activities within its parent organization. In addition, it regularly organizes several traditional activities carried out within the capabilities of its members on an annual basis. These include donations of clothing, food, hygiene products, medicines for the homeless and orphaned children, and books to local libraries in Belgrade and other places in Serbia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://evropa27.org/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://evropa27.org/en/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you wish to contact us, please use the form below.&#xA;Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regular Freemasonry</title>
      <link>https://evropa27.org/en/post/freemasonry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://evropa27.org/en/post/freemasonry/</guid>
      <description>Freemasonry is described as a &amp;ldquo;system of moral values, veiled in allegory and illustrated by symbols.&amp;rdquo; Since Freemasonry is a human creation composed of people and civilization values, every Brother is called to contribute to its development in their way and within the limits of their capabilities, discovering through this process what they carry within themselves. Regular Freemasonry officially began its organized activity by forming the Grand Lodge of England in London in 1717.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
